a
Help me!
Oh yeah!
You kept the lightning locked inside a jar Told
us to smile and play the pop star You muted the
kick, you silenced the crash But we built a fire
from the sparks and the ash Can you feel the
pressure dropping? Can you hear the rhythm
knocking? The glass is cracking, the walls are
thin We're letting the heavy weather in
We are the thunderhead, yeah. Rolling across
the sky. We're waking up the dead, yeah. Kiss the
quiet days goodbye, yeah. A hundred miles an
hour, shaking the ground. This is the fury. This
is the sound.
Oh yeah.
Ten years of machines keeping time in the dark
Now we're striking the middle We're making a
mark The snare is a gunshot The times are a quake
How much of this noise can your system take? Can
you feel the pressure dropping? Can you hear the
rhythm knocking? The glass is cracking, the
walls are thin We're letting the heavy weather
in We are the Thunderheads! Yeah! Rollin'
across the sky! We're waking up the dead, yeah!
Kiss the quiet days goodbye, yeah! A hundred
miles an hour, shaking the ground! This is the
fury! This is the sound!
um um
We're breaking the silence. We're bringing the
storm. We're tearing apart the uniform. Yeah!
We are the thunderhead. Yeah! Rolling across
the sky. We're waking up the dead, yeah Kiss the
quiet days goodbye, yeah A hundred miles an
hour, shaking the ground This is the fury, this
is the sound Bring
the thunder
Shake the crowd, y'all!